{
    "attendees": [
        {
            "costs": {
                "base_price": {
                    "display": "$31.92",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3192,
                    "major_value": "31.92"
                },
                "eventbrite_fee": {
                    "display": "$2.15",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 215,
                    "major_value": "2.15"
                },
                "gross": {
                    "display": "$35.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3500,
                    "major_value": "35.00"
                },
                "payment_fee": {
                    "display": "$0.93",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 93,
                    "major_value": "0.93"
                },
                "tax": {
                    "display": "$0.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 0,
                    "major_value": "0.00"
                }
            },
            "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/999998975197/attendees/0000000001/",
            "id": "0000000001",
            "changed": "2023-03-04T15:01:26Z",
            "created": "2023-03-04T15:01:23Z",
            "quantity": 1,
            "variant_id": null,
            "profile": {
                "first_name": "Loretta",
                "last_name": "Shulman",
                "email": "lshulman@example.com",
                "name": "Loretta Shulman",
                "addresses": []
            },
            "barcodes": [
                {
                    "status": "unused",
                    "barcode": "9999989751978888873619001",
                    "created": "2023-03-04T15:01:27Z",
                    "changed": "2023-03-04T15:01:27Z",
                    "checkin_type": 0,
                    "is_printed": false
                }
            ],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Conditions for Child and Youth membership",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999991879"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Loretta",
                    "question": "Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999994149"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Child Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999998779"
                }
            ],
            "checked_in": false,
            "cancelled": false,
            "refunded": false,
            "affiliate": "oddtdteb",
            "guestlist_id": null,
            "invited_by": null,
            "status": "Attending",
            "ticket_class_name": "Weekend Membership - Tier 1",
            "delivery_method": "electronic",
            "event_id": "999998975197",
            "order_id": "8888873619",
            "ticket_class_id": "999996719"
        },
        {
            "costs": {
                "base_price": {
                    "display": "$31.92",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3192,
                    "major_value": "31.92"
                },
                "eventbrite_fee": {
                    "display": "$2.15",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 215,
                    "major_value": "2.15"
                },
                "gross": {
                    "display": "$35.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3500,
                    "major_value": "35.00"
                },
                "payment_fee": {
                    "display": "$0.93",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 93,
                    "major_value": "0.93"
                },
                "tax": {
                    "display": "$0.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 0,
                    "major_value": "0.00"
                }
            },
            "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/999998975197/attendees/0000000002/",
            "id": "0000000002",
            "changed": "2023-03-04T15:01:42Z",
            "created": "2023-03-04T15:01:39Z",
            "quantity": 1,
            "variant_id": null,
            "profile": {
                "first_name": "Hannis",
                "last_name": "Kasevich",
                "email": "hkasevich@example.com",
                "name": "Hannis Kasevich",
                "addresses": {
                    "bill": {
                        "country": "US",
                        "postal_code": "70001"
                    }
                }
            },
            "barcodes": [
                {
                    "status": "unused",
                    "barcode": "9999989751978888876299002",
                    "created": "2023-03-04T15:01:43Z",
                    "changed": "2023-03-04T15:01:43Z",
                    "checkin_type": 0,
                    "is_printed": false
                }
            ],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Conditions for Child and Youth membership",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999991879"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Hannis",
                    "question": "Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999994149"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Child Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999998779"
                }
            ],
            "checked_in": false,
            "cancelled": false,
            "refunded": false,
            "affiliate": "oddtdteb",
            "guestlist_id": null,
            "invited_by": null,
            "status": "Attending",
            "ticket_class_name": "Weekend Membership - Tier 1",
            "delivery_method": "electronic",
            "event_id": "999998975197",
            "order_id": "8888876299",
            "ticket_class_id": "999996719"
        },
        {
            "costs": {
                "base_price": {
                    "display": "$31.92",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3192,
                    "major_value": "31.92"
                },
                "eventbrite_fee": {
                    "display": "$2.15",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 215,
                    "major_value": "2.15"
                },
                "gross": {
                    "display": "$35.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3500,
                    "major_value": "35.00"
                },
                "payment_fee": {
                    "display": "$0.93",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 93,
                    "major_value": "0.93"
                },
                "tax": {
                    "display": "$0.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 0,
                    "major_value": "0.00"
                }
            },
            "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/999998975197/attendees/0000000003/",
            "id": "0000000003",
            "changed": "2023-03-04T15:02:34Z",
            "created": "2023-03-04T15:02:31Z",
            "quantity": 1,
            "variant_id": null,
            "profile": {
                "first_name": "Deeann",
                "last_name": "Conger",
                "email": "dconger@example.com",
                "name": "Deeann Conger",
                "addresses": {
                    "bill": {
                        "country": "US",
                        "postal_code": "75092"
                    }
                }
            },
            "barcodes": [
                {
                    "status": "unused",
                    "barcode": "9999989751978888874779003",
                    "created": "2023-03-04T15:02:35Z",
                    "changed": "2023-03-04T15:02:35Z",
                    "checkin_type": 0,
                    "is_printed": false
                }
            ],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Conditions for Child and Youth membership",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999991879"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Deeann",
                    "question": "Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999994149"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Child Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999998779"
                }
            ],
            "checked_in": false,
            "cancelled": false,
            "refunded": false,
            "affiliate": "oddtdteb",
            "guestlist_id": null,
            "invited_by": null,
            "status": "Attending",
            "ticket_class_name": "Weekend Membership - Tier 1",
            "delivery_method": "electronic",
            "event_id": "999998975197",
            "order_id": "8888874779",
            "ticket_class_id": "999996719"
        },
        {
            "costs": {
                "base_price": {
                    "display": "$31.92",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3192,
                    "major_value": "31.92"
                },
                "eventbrite_fee": {
                    "display": "$2.15",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 215,
                    "major_value": "2.15"
                },
                "gross": {
                    "display": "$35.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3500,
                    "major_value": "35.00"
                },
                "payment_fee": {
                    "display": "$0.93",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 93,
                    "major_value": "0.93"
                },
                "tax": {
                    "display": "$0.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 0,
                    "major_value": "0.00"
                }
            },
            "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/999998975197/attendees/0000000004/",
            "id": "0000000004",
            "changed": "2023-03-04T15:03:05Z",
            "created": "2023-03-04T15:03:01Z",
            "quantity": 1,
            "variant_id": null,
            "profile": {
                "first_name": "Revkah",
                "last_name": "Cecily",
                "email": "rcecily@example.com",
                "name": "Revkah Cecily",
                "addresses": {
                    "bill": {
                        "country": "US",
                        "postal_code": "76104"
                    }
                }
            },
            "barcodes": [
                {
                    "status": "unused",
                    "barcode": "9999989751978888885559004",
                    "created": "2023-03-04T15:03:05Z",
                    "changed": "2023-03-04T15:03:05Z",
                    "checkin_type": 0,
                    "is_printed": false
                }
            ],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Conditions for Child and Youth membership",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999991879"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Revkah",
                    "question": "Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999994149"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Child Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999998779"
                }
            ],
            "checked_in": false,
            "cancelled": false,
            "refunded": false,
            "affiliate": "oddtdteb",
            "guestlist_id": null,
            "invited_by": null,
            "status": "Attending",
            "ticket_class_name": "Weekend Membership - Tier 1",
            "delivery_method": "electronic",
            "event_id": "999998975197",
            "order_id": "8888885559",
            "ticket_class_id": "999996719"
        },
        {
            "costs": {
                "base_price": {
                    "display": "$31.92",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3192,
                    "major_value": "31.92"
                },
                "eventbrite_fee": {
                    "display": "$2.15",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 215,
                    "major_value": "2.15"
                },
                "gross": {
                    "display": "$35.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3500,
                    "major_value": "35.00"
                },
                "payment_fee": {
                    "display": "$0.93",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 93,
                    "major_value": "0.93"
                },
                "tax": {
                    "display": "$0.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 0,
                    "major_value": "0.00"
                }
            },
            "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/999998975197/attendees/0000000005/",
            "id": "0000000005",
            "changed": "2023-03-04T15:03:06Z",
            "created": "2023-03-04T15:03:03Z",
            "quantity": 1,
            "variant_id": null,
            "profile": {
                "first_name": "Jazmin",
                "last_name": "Mani",
                "email": "jmani@example.com",
                "name": "Jazmin Mani",
                "addresses": {
                    "bill": {
                        "country": "US",
                        "postal_code": "75081"
                    }
                }
            },
            "barcodes": [
                {
                    "status": "unused",
                    "barcode": "9999989751978888884209005",
                    "created": "2023-03-04T15:03:06Z",
                    "changed": "2023-03-04T15:03:06Z",
                    "checkin_type": 0,
                    "is_printed": false
                }
            ],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Conditions for Child and Youth membership",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999991879"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Jazmin",
                    "question": "Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999994149"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Child Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999998779"
                }
            ],
            "checked_in": false,
            "cancelled": false,
            "refunded": false,
            "affiliate": "oddtdteb",
            "guestlist_id": null,
            "invited_by": null,
            "status": "Attending",
            "ticket_class_name": "Weekend Membership - Tier 1",
            "delivery_method": "electronic",
            "event_id": "999998975197",
            "order_id": "8888884209",
            "ticket_class_id": "999996719"
        },
        {
            "costs": {
                "base_price": {
                    "display": "$31.92",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3192,
                    "major_value": "31.92"
                },
                "eventbrite_fee": {
                    "display": "$2.15",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 215,
                    "major_value": "2.15"
                },
                "gross": {
                    "display": "$35.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3500,
                    "major_value": "35.00"
                },
                "payment_fee": {
                    "display": "$0.93",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 93,
                    "major_value": "0.93"
                },
                "tax": {
                    "display": "$0.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 0,
                    "major_value": "0.00"
                }
            },
            "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/999998975197/attendees/0000000006/",
            "id": "0000000006",
            "changed": "2023-03-04T15:03:20Z",
            "created": "2023-03-04T15:03:16Z",
            "quantity": 1,
            "variant_id": null,
            "profile": {
                "first_name": "Harmonia",
                "last_name": "Goff",
                "email": "hgoff@example.com",
                "name": "Harmonia Goff",
                "addresses": {
                    "bill": {
                        "country": "US",
                        "postal_code": "74075"
                    }
                }
            },
            "barcodes": [
                {
                    "status": "unused",
                    "barcode": "9999989751978888880559006",
                    "created": "2023-03-04T15:03:20Z",
                    "changed": "2023-03-04T15:03:20Z",
                    "checkin_type": 0,
                    "is_printed": false
                }
            ],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Conditions for Child and Youth membership",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999991879"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Harmonia",
                    "question": "Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999994149"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Child Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999998779"
                }
            ],
            "checked_in": false,
            "cancelled": false,
            "refunded": false,
            "affiliate": "oddtdteb",
            "guestlist_id": null,
            "invited_by": null,
            "status": "Attending",
            "ticket_class_name": "Weekend Membership - Tier 1",
            "delivery_method": "electronic",
            "event_id": "999998975197",
            "order_id": "8888880559",
            "ticket_class_id": "999996719"
        },
        {
            "costs": {
                "base_price": {
                    "display": "$31.92",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3192,
                    "major_value": "31.92"
                },
                "eventbrite_fee": {
                    "display": "$2.15",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 215,
                    "major_value": "2.15"
                },
                "gross": {
                    "display": "$35.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3500,
                    "major_value": "35.00"
                },
                "payment_fee": {
                    "display": "$0.93",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 93,
                    "major_value": "0.93"
                },
                "tax": {
                    "display": "$0.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 0,
                    "major_value": "0.00"
                }
            },
            "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/999998975197/attendees/0000000007/",
            "id": "0000000007",
            "changed": "2023-03-04T15:03:20Z",
            "created": "2023-03-04T15:03:16Z",
            "quantity": 1,
            "variant_id": null,
            "profile": {
                "first_name": "Petra",
                "last_name": "McKee",
                "email": "pmckee@example.com",
                "name": "Petra McKee",
                "addresses": {
                    "bill": {
                        "country": "US",
                        "postal_code": "74075"
                    }
                }
            },
            "barcodes": [
                {
                    "status": "unused",
                    "barcode": "9999989751978888880559007",
                    "created": "2023-03-04T15:03:20Z",
                    "changed": "2023-03-04T15:03:20Z",
                    "checkin_type": 0,
                    "is_printed": false
                }
            ],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Conditions for Child and Youth membership",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999991879"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Petra",
                    "question": "Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999994149"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Child Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999998779"
                }
            ],
            "checked_in": false,
            "cancelled": false,
            "refunded": false,
            "affiliate": "oddtdteb",
            "guestlist_id": null,
            "invited_by": null,
            "status": "Attending",
            "ticket_class_name": "Weekend Membership - Tier 1",
            "delivery_method": "electronic",
            "event_id": "999998975197",
            "order_id": "8888880559",
            "ticket_class_id": "999996719"
        },
        {
            "costs": {
                "base_price": {
                    "display": "$31.92",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3192,
                    "major_value": "31.92"
                },
                "eventbrite_fee": {
                    "display": "$2.15",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 215,
                    "major_value": "2.15"
                },
                "gross": {
                    "display": "$35.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3500,
                    "major_value": "35.00"
                },
                "payment_fee": {
                    "display": "$0.93",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 93,
                    "major_value": "0.93"
                },
                "tax": {
                    "display": "$0.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 0,
                    "major_value": "0.00"
                }
            },
            "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/999998975197/attendees/0000000008/",
            "id": "0000000008",
            "changed": "2023-03-04T15:03:31Z",
            "created": "2023-03-04T15:03:28Z",
            "quantity": 1,
            "variant_id": null,
            "profile": {
                "first_name": "Bernette",
                "last_name": "Corbett",
                "email": "bcorbett@example.com",
                "name": "Bernette Corbett",
                "addresses": {
                    "bill": {
                        "country": "US",
                        "postal_code": "76104"
                    }
                }
            },
            "barcodes": [
                {
                    "status": "unused",
                    "barcode": "9999989751978888885029008",
                    "created": "2023-03-04T15:03:31Z",
                    "changed": "2023-03-04T15:03:31Z",
                    "checkin_type": 0,
                    "is_printed": false
                }
            ],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Conditions for Child and Youth membership",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999991879"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Bernette",
                    "question": "Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999994149"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Child Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999998779"
                }
            ],
            "checked_in": false,
            "cancelled": false,
            "refunded": false,
            "affiliate": "oddtdteb",
            "guestlist_id": null,
            "invited_by": null,
            "status": "Attending",
            "ticket_class_name": "Weekend Membership - Tier 1",
            "delivery_method": "electronic",
            "event_id": "999998975197",
            "order_id": "8888885029",
            "ticket_class_id": "999996719"
        },
        {
            "costs": {
                "base_price": {
                    "display": "$31.92",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3192,
                    "major_value": "31.92"
                },
                "eventbrite_fee": {
                    "display": "$2.15",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 215,
                    "major_value": "2.15"
                },
                "gross": {
                    "display": "$35.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3500,
                    "major_value": "35.00"
                },
                "payment_fee": {
                    "display": "$0.93",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 93,
                    "major_value": "0.93"
                },
                "tax": {
                    "display": "$0.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 0,
                    "major_value": "0.00"
                }
            },
            "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/999998975197/attendees/0000000009/",
            "id": "0000000009",
            "changed": "2023-03-04T15:04:05Z",
            "created": "2023-03-04T15:04:01Z",
            "quantity": 1,
            "variant_id": null,
            "profile": {
                "first_name": "Dorelia",
                "last_name": "McMahon",
                "email": "dmcmahon@example.com",
                "name": "Dorelia McMahon",
                "addresses": []
            },
            "barcodes": [
                {
                    "status": "unused",
                    "barcode": "9999989751978888877229009",
                    "created": "2023-03-04T15:04:05Z",
                    "changed": "2023-03-04T15:04:05Z",
                    "checkin_type": 0,
                    "is_printed": false
                }
            ],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Conditions for Child and Youth membership",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999991879"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Dorelia",
                    "question": "Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999994149"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Child Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999998779"
                }
            ],
            "checked_in": false,
            "cancelled": false,
            "refunded": false,
            "affiliate": "oddtdteb",
            "guestlist_id": null,
            "invited_by": null,
            "status": "Attending",
            "ticket_class_name": "Weekend Membership - Tier 1",
            "delivery_method": "electronic",
            "event_id": "999998975197",
            "order_id": "8888877229",
            "ticket_class_id": "999996719"
        },
        {
            "costs": {
                "base_price": {
                    "display": "$31.92",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3192,
                    "major_value": "31.92"
                },
                "eventbrite_fee": {
                    "display": "$2.15",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 215,
                    "major_value": "2.15"
                },
                "gross": {
                    "display": "$35.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3500,
                    "major_value": "35.00"
                },
                "payment_fee": {
                    "display": "$0.93",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 93,
                    "major_value": "0.93"
                },
                "tax": {
                    "display": "$0.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 0,
                    "major_value": "0.00"
                }
            },
            "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/999998975197/attendees/0000000010/",
            "id": "0000000010",
            "changed": "2023-03-04T15:04:05Z",
            "created": "2023-03-04T15:04:01Z",
            "quantity": 1,
            "variant_id": null,
            "profile": {
                "first_name": "Letizia",
                "last_name": "Malamut",
                "email": "lmalamut@example.com",
                "name": "Letizia Malamut",
                "addresses": []
            },
            "barcodes": [
                {
                    "status": "unused",
                    "barcode": "9999989751978888877229010",
                    "created": "2023-03-04T15:04:05Z",
                    "changed": "2023-03-04T15:04:05Z",
                    "checkin_type": 0,
                    "is_printed": false
                }
            ],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Conditions for Child and Youth membership",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999991879"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Letizia",
                    "question": "Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999994149"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Child Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999998779"
                }
            ],
            "checked_in": false,
            "cancelled": false,
            "refunded": false,
            "affiliate": "oddtdteb",
            "guestlist_id": null,
            "invited_by": null,
            "status": "Attending",
            "ticket_class_name": "Weekend Membership - Tier 1",
            "delivery_method": "electronic",
            "event_id": "999998975197",
            "order_id": "8888877229",
            "ticket_class_id": "999996719"
        },
        {
            "costs": {
                "base_price": {
                    "display": "$31.92",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3192,
                    "major_value": "31.92"
                },
                "eventbrite_fee": {
                    "display": "$2.15",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 215,
                    "major_value": "2.15"
                },
                "gross": {
                    "display": "$35.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3500,
                    "major_value": "35.00"
                },
                "payment_fee": {
                    "display": "$0.93",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 93,
                    "major_value": "0.93"
                },
                "tax": {
                    "display": "$0.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 0,
                    "major_value": "0.00"
                }
            },
            "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/999998975197/attendees/0000000011/",
            "id": "0000000011",
            "changed": "2023-03-04T15:04:08Z",
            "created": "2023-03-04T15:04:04Z",
            "quantity": 1,
            "variant_id": null,
            "profile": {
                "first_name": "Storm",
                "last_name": "Cece",
                "email": "scece@example.com",
                "name": "Storm Cece",
                "addresses": {
                    "bill": {
                        "country": "US",
                        "postal_code": "75166"
                    }
                }
            },
            "barcodes": [
                {
                    "status": "unused",
                    "barcode": "9999989751978888892589011",
                    "created": "2023-03-04T15:04:09Z",
                    "changed": "2023-03-04T15:04:09Z",
                    "checkin_type": 0,
                    "is_printed": false
                }
            ],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Conditions for Child and Youth membership",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999991879"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Storm",
                    "question": "Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999994149"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Child Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999998779"
                }
            ],
            "checked_in": false,
            "cancelled": false,
            "refunded": false,
            "affiliate": "oddtdteb",
            "guestlist_id": null,
            "invited_by": null,
            "status": "Attending",
            "ticket_class_name": "Weekend Membership - Tier 1",
            "delivery_method": "electronic",
            "event_id": "999998975197",
            "order_id": "8888892589",
            "ticket_class_id": "999996719"
        },
        {
            "costs": {
                "base_price": {
                    "display": "$31.92",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3192,
                    "major_value": "31.92"
                },
                "eventbrite_fee": {
                    "display": "$2.15",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 215,
                    "major_value": "2.15"
                },
                "gross": {
                    "display": "$35.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3500,
                    "major_value": "35.00"
                },
                "payment_fee": {
                    "display": "$0.93",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 93,
                    "major_value": "0.93"
                },
                "tax": {
                    "display": "$0.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 0,
                    "major_value": "0.00"
                }
            },
            "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/999998975197/attendees/0000000012/",
            "id": "0000000012",
            "changed": "2023-03-04T15:04:10Z",
            "created": "2023-03-04T15:04:07Z",
            "quantity": 1,
            "variant_id": null,
            "profile": {
                "first_name": "Rhodia",
                "last_name": "Jesh",
                "email": "rjesh@example.com",
                "name": "Rhodia Jesh",
                "addresses": {
                    "bill": {
                        "country": "US",
                        "postal_code": "75028"
                    }
                }
            },
            "barcodes": [
                {
                    "status": "unused",
                    "barcode": "9999989751978888886679012",
                    "created": "2023-03-04T15:04:11Z",
                    "changed": "2023-03-04T15:04:11Z",
                    "checkin_type": 0,
                    "is_printed": false
                }
            ],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Conditions for Child and Youth membership",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999991879"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Rhodia",
                    "question": "Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999994149"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Child Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999998779"
                }
            ],
            "checked_in": false,
            "cancelled": false,
            "refunded": false,
            "affiliate": "oddtdteb",
            "guestlist_id": null,
            "invited_by": null,
            "status": "Attending",
            "ticket_class_name": "Weekend Membership - Tier 1",
            "delivery_method": "electronic",
            "event_id": "999998975197",
            "order_id": "8888886679",
            "ticket_class_id": "999996719"
        },
        {
            "costs": {
                "base_price": {
                    "display": "$31.92",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3192,
                    "major_value": "31.92"
                },
                "eventbrite_fee": {
                    "display": "$2.15",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 215,
                    "major_value": "2.15"
                },
                "gross": {
                    "display": "$35.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3500,
                    "major_value": "35.00"
                },
                "payment_fee": {
                    "display": "$0.93",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 93,
                    "major_value": "0.93"
                },
                "tax": {
                    "display": "$0.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 0,
                    "major_value": "0.00"
                }
            },
            "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/999998975197/attendees/0000000013/",
            "id": "0000000013",
            "changed": "2023-03-04T15:04:10Z",
            "created": "2023-03-04T15:04:07Z",
            "quantity": 1,
            "variant_id": null,
            "profile": {
                "first_name": "Jammie",
                "last_name": "Lindsy",
                "email": "jlindsy@example.com",
                "name": "Jammie Lindsy",
                "addresses": {
                    "bill": {
                        "country": "US",
                        "postal_code": "75028"
                    }
                }
            },
            "barcodes": [
                {
                    "status": "unused",
                    "barcode": "9999989751978888886679013",
                    "created": "2023-03-04T15:04:11Z",
                    "changed": "2023-03-04T15:04:11Z",
                    "checkin_type": 0,
                    "is_printed": false
                }
            ],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Conditions for Child and Youth membership",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999991879"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Jammie",
                    "question": "Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999994149"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Child Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999998779"
                }
            ],
            "checked_in": false,
            "cancelled": false,
            "refunded": false,
            "affiliate": "oddtdteb",
            "guestlist_id": null,
            "invited_by": null,
            "status": "Attending",
            "ticket_class_name": "Weekend Membership - Tier 1",
            "delivery_method": "electronic",
            "event_id": "999998975197",
            "order_id": "8888886679",
            "ticket_class_id": "999996719"
        },
        {
            "costs": {
                "base_price": {
                    "display": "$31.92",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3192,
                    "major_value": "31.92"
                },
                "eventbrite_fee": {
                    "display": "$2.15",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 215,
                    "major_value": "2.15"
                },
                "gross": {
                    "display": "$35.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3500,
                    "major_value": "35.00"
                },
                "payment_fee": {
                    "display": "$0.93",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 93,
                    "major_value": "0.93"
                },
                "tax": {
                    "display": "$0.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 0,
                    "major_value": "0.00"
                }
            },
            "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/999998975197/attendees/0000000014/",
            "id": "0000000014",
            "changed": "2023-03-04T15:04:15Z",
            "created": "2023-03-04T15:04:11Z",
            "quantity": 1,
            "variant_id": null,
            "profile": {
                "first_name": "Adelice",
                "last_name": "Attlee",
                "email": "aattlee@example.com",
                "name": "Adelice Attlee",
                "addresses": []
            },
            "barcodes": [
                {
                    "status": "unused",
                    "barcode": "9999989751978888898299014",
                    "created": "2023-03-04T15:04:16Z",
                    "changed": "2023-03-04T15:04:16Z",
                    "checkin_type": 0,
                    "is_printed": false
                }
            ],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Conditions for Child and Youth membership",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999991879"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Adelice",
                    "question": "Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999994149"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Child Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999998779"
                }
            ],
            "checked_in": false,
            "cancelled": false,
            "refunded": false,
            "affiliate": "ebesesdeeplink",
            "guestlist_id": null,
            "invited_by": null,
            "status": "Attending",
            "ticket_class_name": "Weekend Membership - Tier 1",
            "delivery_method": "electronic",
            "event_id": "999998975197",
            "order_id": "8888898299",
            "ticket_class_id": "999996719"
        },
        {
            "costs": {
                "base_price": {
                    "display": "$31.92",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3192,
                    "major_value": "31.92"
                },
                "eventbrite_fee": {
                    "display": "$2.15",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 215,
                    "major_value": "2.15"
                },
                "gross": {
                    "display": "$35.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3500,
                    "major_value": "35.00"
                },
                "payment_fee": {
                    "display": "$0.93",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 93,
                    "major_value": "0.93"
                },
                "tax": {
                    "display": "$0.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 0,
                    "major_value": "0.00"
                }
            },
            "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/999998975197/attendees/0000000015/",
            "id": "0000000015",
            "changed": "2023-03-04T15:04:18Z",
            "created": "2023-03-04T15:04:15Z",
            "quantity": 1,
            "variant_id": null,
            "profile": {
                "first_name": "Ophelie",
                "last_name": "Vivyanne",
                "email": "ovivyanne@example.com",
                "name": "Ophelie Vivyanne",
                "addresses": []
            },
            "barcodes": [
                {
                    "status": "unused",
                    "barcode": "9999989751978888894669015",
                    "created": "2023-03-04T15:04:18Z",
                    "changed": "2023-03-04T15:04:18Z",
                    "checkin_type": 0,
                    "is_printed": false
                }
            ],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Conditions for Child and Youth membership",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999991879"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Ophelie",
                    "question": "Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999994149"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Child Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999998779"
                }
            ],
            "checked_in": false,
            "cancelled": false,
            "refunded": false,
            "affiliate": "oddtdteb",
            "guestlist_id": null,
            "invited_by": null,
            "status": "Attending",
            "ticket_class_name": "Weekend Membership - Tier 1",
            "delivery_method": "electronic",
            "event_id": "999998975197",
            "order_id": "8888894669",
            "ticket_class_id": "999996719"
        },
        {
            "costs": {
                "base_price": {
                    "display": "$31.92",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3192,
                    "major_value": "31.92"
                },
                "eventbrite_fee": {
                    "display": "$2.15",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 215,
                    "major_value": "2.15"
                },
                "gross": {
                    "display": "$35.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3500,
                    "major_value": "35.00"
                },
                "payment_fee": {
                    "display": "$0.93",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 93,
                    "major_value": "0.93"
                },
                "tax": {
                    "display": "$0.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 0,
                    "major_value": "0.00"
                }
            },
            "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/999998975197/attendees/0000000016/",
            "id": "0000000016",
            "changed": "2023-03-04T15:04:32Z",
            "created": "2023-03-04T15:04:29Z",
            "quantity": 1,
            "variant_id": null,
            "profile": {
                "first_name": "Stacee",
                "last_name": "Trinl",
                "email": "strinl@example.com",
                "name": "Stacee Trinl",
                "addresses": {
                    "bill": {
                        "country": "US",
                        "postal_code": "78393"
                    }
                }
            },
            "barcodes": [
                {
                    "status": "unused",
                    "barcode": "9999989751978888886049016",
                    "created": "2023-03-04T15:04:33Z",
                    "changed": "2023-03-04T15:04:33Z",
                    "checkin_type": 0,
                    "is_printed": false
                }
            ],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Conditions for Child and Youth membership",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999991879"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Stacee",
                    "question": "Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999994149"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Child Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999998779"
                }
            ],
            "checked_in": false,
            "cancelled": false,
            "refunded": false,
            "affiliate": "oddtdteb",
            "guestlist_id": null,
            "invited_by": null,
            "status": "Attending",
            "ticket_class_name": "Weekend Membership - Tier 1",
            "delivery_method": "electronic",
            "event_id": "999998975197",
            "order_id": "8888886049",
            "ticket_class_id": "999996719"
        },
        {
            "costs": {
                "base_price": {
                    "display": "$31.92",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3192,
                    "major_value": "31.92"
                },
                "eventbrite_fee": {
                    "display": "$2.15",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 215,
                    "major_value": "2.15"
                },
                "gross": {
                    "display": "$35.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3500,
                    "major_value": "35.00"
                },
                "payment_fee": {
                    "display": "$0.93",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 93,
                    "major_value": "0.93"
                },
                "tax": {
                    "display": "$0.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 0,
                    "major_value": "0.00"
                }
            },
            "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/999998975197/attendees/0000000017/",
            "id": "0000000017",
            "changed": "2023-03-04T15:04:32Z",
            "created": "2023-03-04T15:04:29Z",
            "quantity": 1,
            "variant_id": null,
            "profile": {
                "first_name": "Blinnie",
                "last_name": "Balcer",
                "email": "bbalcer@example.com",
                "name": "Blinnie Balcer",
                "addresses": {
                    "bill": {
                        "country": "US",
                        "postal_code": "78393"
                    }
                }
            },
            "barcodes": [
                {
                    "status": "unused",
                    "barcode": "9999989751978888886049017",
                    "created": "2023-03-04T15:04:33Z",
                    "changed": "2023-03-04T15:04:33Z",
                    "checkin_type": 0,
                    "is_printed": false
                }
            ],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Conditions for Child and Youth membership",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999991879"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Blinnie",
                    "question": "Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999994149"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Child Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999998779"
                }
            ],
            "checked_in": false,
            "cancelled": false,
            "refunded": false,
            "affiliate": "oddtdteb",
            "guestlist_id": null,
            "invited_by": null,
            "status": "Attending",
            "ticket_class_name": "Weekend Membership - Tier 1",
            "delivery_method": "electronic",
            "event_id": "999998975197",
            "order_id": "8888886049",
            "ticket_class_id": "999996719"
        },
        {
            "costs": {
                "base_price": {
                    "display": "$31.92",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3192,
                    "major_value": "31.92"
                },
                "eventbrite_fee": {
                    "display": "$2.15",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 215,
                    "major_value": "2.15"
                },
                "gross": {
                    "display": "$35.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3500,
                    "major_value": "35.00"
                },
                "payment_fee": {
                    "display": "$0.93",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 93,
                    "major_value": "0.93"
                },
                "tax": {
                    "display": "$0.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 0,
                    "major_value": "0.00"
                }
            },
            "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/999998975197/attendees/0000000018/",
            "id": "0000000018",
            "changed": "2023-03-04T15:04:43Z",
            "created": "2023-03-04T15:04:38Z",
            "quantity": 1,
            "variant_id": null,
            "profile": {
                "first_name": "Truda",
                "last_name": "Vlada",
                "email": "tvlada@example.com",
                "name": "Truda Vlada",
                "addresses": []
            },
            "barcodes": [
                {
                    "status": "unused",
                    "barcode": "9999989751978888892019018",
                    "created": "2023-03-04T15:04:44Z",
                    "changed": "2023-03-04T15:04:44Z",
                    "checkin_type": 0,
                    "is_printed": false
                }
            ],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Conditions for Child and Youth membership",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999991879"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Truda",
                    "question": "Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999994149"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Child Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999998779"
                }
            ],
            "checked_in": false,
            "cancelled": false,
            "refunded": false,
            "affiliate": "oddtdteb",
            "guestlist_id": null,
            "invited_by": null,
            "status": "Attending",
            "ticket_class_name": "Weekend Membership - Tier 1",
            "delivery_method": "electronic",
            "event_id": "999998975197",
            "order_id": "8888892019",
            "ticket_class_id": "999996719"
        },
        {
            "costs": {
                "base_price": {
                    "display": "$31.92",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3192,
                    "major_value": "31.92"
                },
                "eventbrite_fee": {
                    "display": "$2.15",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 215,
                    "major_value": "2.15"
                },
                "gross": {
                    "display": "$35.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3500,
                    "major_value": "35.00"
                },
                "payment_fee": {
                    "display": "$0.93",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 93,
                    "major_value": "0.93"
                },
                "tax": {
                    "display": "$0.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 0,
                    "major_value": "0.00"
                }
            },
            "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/999998975197/attendees/0000000019/",
            "id": "0000000019",
            "changed": "2023-03-04T15:04:43Z",
            "created": "2023-03-04T15:04:38Z",
            "quantity": 1,
            "variant_id": null,
            "profile": {
                "first_name": "Tabatha",
                "last_name": "Ress",
                "email": "tress@example.com",
                "name": "Tabatha Ress",
                "addresses": []
            },
            "barcodes": [
                {
                    "status": "unused",
                    "barcode": "9999989751978888892019019",
                    "created": "2023-03-04T15:04:44Z",
                    "changed": "2023-03-04T15:04:44Z",
                    "checkin_type": 0,
                    "is_printed": false
                }
            ],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Conditions for Child and Youth membership",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999991879"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Tabatha",
                    "question": "Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999994149"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Child Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999998779"
                }
            ],
            "checked_in": false,
            "cancelled": false,
            "refunded": false,
            "affiliate": "oddtdteb",
            "guestlist_id": null,
            "invited_by": null,
            "status": "Attending",
            "ticket_class_name": "Weekend Membership - Tier 1",
            "delivery_method": "electronic",
            "event_id": "999998975197",
            "order_id": "8888892019",
            "ticket_class_id": "999996719"
        },
        {
            "costs": {
                "base_price": {
                    "display": "$31.92",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3192,
                    "major_value": "31.92"
                },
                "eventbrite_fee": {
                    "display": "$2.15",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 215,
                    "major_value": "2.15"
                },
                "gross": {
                    "display": "$35.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3500,
                    "major_value": "35.00"
                },
                "payment_fee": {
                    "display": "$0.93",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 93,
                    "major_value": "0.93"
                },
                "tax": {
                    "display": "$0.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 0,
                    "major_value": "0.00"
                }
            },
            "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/999998975197/attendees/0000000020/",
            "id": "0000000020",
            "changed": "2023-03-04T15:05:41Z",
            "created": "2023-03-04T15:05:36Z",
            "quantity": 1,
            "variant_id": null,
            "profile": {
                "first_name": "Margaretha",
                "last_name": "Teri",
                "email": "mteri@example.com",
                "name": "Margaretha Teri",
                "addresses": []
            },
            "barcodes": [
                {
                    "status": "unused",
                    "barcode": "9999989751978888893729020",
                    "created": "2023-03-04T15:05:41Z",
                    "changed": "2023-03-04T15:05:41Z",
                    "checkin_type": 0,
                    "is_printed": false
                }
            ],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Conditions for Child and Youth membership",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999991879"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Margaretha",
                    "question": "Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999994149"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Child Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999998779"
                }
            ],
            "checked_in": false,
            "cancelled": false,
            "refunded": false,
            "affiliate": "oddtdteb",
            "guestlist_id": null,
            "invited_by": null,
            "status": "Attending",
            "ticket_class_name": "Weekend Membership - Tier 1",
            "delivery_method": "electronic",
            "event_id": "999998975197",
            "order_id": "8888893729",
            "ticket_class_id": "999996719"
        },
        {
            "costs": {
                "base_price": {
                    "display": "$31.92",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3192,
                    "major_value": "31.92"
                },
                "eventbrite_fee": {
                    "display": "$2.15",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 215,
                    "major_value": "2.15"
                },
                "gross": {
                    "display": "$35.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3500,
                    "major_value": "35.00"
                },
                "payment_fee": {
                    "display": "$0.93",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 93,
                    "major_value": "0.93"
                },
                "tax": {
                    "display": "$0.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 0,
                    "major_value": "0.00"
                }
            },
            "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/999998975197/attendees/0000000021/",
            "id": "0000000021",
            "changed": "2023-03-04T15:05:41Z",
            "created": "2023-03-04T15:05:36Z",
            "quantity": 1,
            "variant_id": null,
            "profile": {
                "first_name": "Raphaela",
                "last_name": "Cuttler",
                "email": "rcuttler@example.com",
                "name": "Raphaela Cuttler",
                "addresses": []
            },
            "barcodes": [
                {
                    "status": "unused",
                    "barcode": "9999989751978888893729021",
                    "created": "2023-03-04T15:05:41Z",
                    "changed": "2023-03-04T15:05:41Z",
                    "checkin_type": 0,
                    "is_printed": false
                }
            ],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Conditions for Child and Youth membership",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999991879"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Raphaela",
                    "question": "Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999994149"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Child Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999998779"
                }
            ],
            "checked_in": false,
            "cancelled": false,
            "refunded": false,
            "affiliate": "oddtdteb",
            "guestlist_id": null,
            "invited_by": null,
            "status": "Attending",
            "ticket_class_name": "Weekend Membership - Tier 1",
            "delivery_method": "electronic",
            "event_id": "999998975197",
            "order_id": "8888893729",
            "ticket_class_id": "999996719"
        },
        {
            "costs": {
                "base_price": {
                    "display": "$31.92",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3192,
                    "major_value": "31.92"
                },
                "eventbrite_fee": {
                    "display": "$2.15",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 215,
                    "major_value": "2.15"
                },
                "gross": {
                    "display": "$35.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3500,
                    "major_value": "35.00"
                },
                "payment_fee": {
                    "display": "$0.93",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 93,
                    "major_value": "0.93"
                },
                "tax": {
                    "display": "$0.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 0,
                    "major_value": "0.00"
                }
            },
            "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/999998975197/attendees/0000000022/",
            "id": "0000000022",
            "changed": "2023-03-04T15:06:08Z",
            "created": "2023-03-04T15:06:05Z",
            "quantity": 1,
            "variant_id": null,
            "profile": {
                "first_name": "Leone",
                "last_name": "Zetes",
                "email": "lzetes@example.com",
                "name": "Leone Zetes",
                "addresses": {
                    "bill": {
                        "country": "US",
                        "postal_code": "75023"
                    }
                }
            },
            "barcodes": [
                {
                    "status": "unused",
                    "barcode": "9999989751978888805459022",
                    "created": "2023-03-04T15:06:08Z",
                    "changed": "2023-03-04T15:06:08Z",
                    "checkin_type": 0,
                    "is_printed": false
                }
            ],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Conditions for Child and Youth membership",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999991879"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Leone",
                    "question": "Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999994149"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Child Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999998779"
                }
            ],
            "checked_in": false,
            "cancelled": false,
            "refunded": false,
            "affiliate": "oddtdteb",
            "guestlist_id": null,
            "invited_by": null,
            "status": "Attending",
            "ticket_class_name": "Weekend Membership - Tier 1",
            "delivery_method": "electronic",
            "event_id": "999998975197",
            "order_id": "8888805459",
            "ticket_class_id": "999996719"
        },
        {
            "costs": {
                "base_price": {
                    "display": "$31.92",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3192,
                    "major_value": "31.92"
                },
                "eventbrite_fee": {
                    "display": "$2.15",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 215,
                    "major_value": "2.15"
                },
                "gross": {
                    "display": "$35.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3500,
                    "major_value": "35.00"
                },
                "payment_fee": {
                    "display": "$0.93",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 93,
                    "major_value": "0.93"
                },
                "tax": {
                    "display": "$0.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 0,
                    "major_value": "0.00"
                }
            },
            "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/999998975197/attendees/0000000023/",
            "id": "0000000023",
            "changed": "2023-03-04T15:06:09Z",
            "created": "2023-03-04T15:06:04Z",
            "quantity": 1,
            "variant_id": null,
            "profile": {
                "first_name": "Dru",
                "last_name": "Hughmanick",
                "email": "dhughmanick@example.com",
                "name": "Dru Hughmanick",
                "addresses": []
            },
            "barcodes": [
                {
                    "status": "unused",
                    "barcode": "9999989751978888890679023",
                    "created": "2023-03-04T15:06:09Z",
                    "changed": "2023-03-04T15:06:09Z",
                    "checkin_type": 0,
                    "is_printed": false
                }
            ],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Conditions for Child and Youth membership",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999991879"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Dru",
                    "question": "Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999994149"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Child Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999998779"
                }
            ],
            "checked_in": false,
            "cancelled": false,
            "refunded": false,
            "affiliate": "oddtdteb",
            "guestlist_id": null,
            "invited_by": null,
            "status": "Attending",
            "ticket_class_name": "Weekend Membership - Tier 1",
            "delivery_method": "electronic",
            "event_id": "999998975197",
            "order_id": "8888890679",
            "ticket_class_id": "999996719"
        },
        {
            "costs": {
                "base_price": {
                    "display": "$31.92",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3192,
                    "major_value": "31.92"
                },
                "eventbrite_fee": {
                    "display": "$2.15",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 215,
                    "major_value": "2.15"
                },
                "gross": {
                    "display": "$35.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3500,
                    "major_value": "35.00"
                },
                "payment_fee": {
                    "display": "$0.93",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 93,
                    "major_value": "0.93"
                },
                "tax": {
                    "display": "$0.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 0,
                    "major_value": "0.00"
                }
            },
            "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/999998975197/attendees/0000000024/",
            "id": "0000000024",
            "changed": "2023-03-04T15:06:11Z",
            "created": "2023-03-04T15:06:08Z",
            "quantity": 1,
            "variant_id": null,
            "profile": {
                "first_name": "Nessa",
                "last_name": "Alia",
                "email": "nalia@example.com",
                "name": "Nessa Alia",
                "addresses": []
            },
            "barcodes": [
                {
                    "status": "unused",
                    "barcode": "9999989751978888896729024",
                    "created": "2023-03-04T15:06:12Z",
                    "changed": "2023-03-04T15:06:12Z",
                    "checkin_type": 0,
                    "is_printed": false
                }
            ],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Conditions for Child and Youth membership",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999991879"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Nessa",
                    "question": "Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999994149"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Child Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999998779"
                }
            ],
            "checked_in": false,
            "cancelled": false,
            "refunded": false,
            "affiliate": "oddtdteb",
            "guestlist_id": null,
            "invited_by": null,
            "status": "Attending",
            "ticket_class_name": "Weekend Membership - Tier 1",
            "delivery_method": "electronic",
            "event_id": "999998975197",
            "order_id": "8888896729",
            "ticket_class_id": "999996719"
        },
        {
            "costs": {
                "base_price": {
                    "display": "$31.92",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3192,
                    "major_value": "31.92"
                },
                "eventbrite_fee": {
                    "display": "$2.15",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 215,
                    "major_value": "2.15"
                },
                "gross": {
                    "display": "$35.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3500,
                    "major_value": "35.00"
                },
                "payment_fee": {
                    "display": "$0.93",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 93,
                    "major_value": "0.93"
                },
                "tax": {
                    "display": "$0.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 0,
                    "major_value": "0.00"
                }
            },
            "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/999998975197/attendees/0000000025/",
            "id": "0000000025",
            "changed": "2023-03-04T15:06:18Z",
            "created": "2023-03-04T15:06:16Z",
            "quantity": 1,
            "variant_id": null,
            "profile": {
                "first_name": "Vinita",
                "last_name": "Ji",
                "email": "vji@example.com",
                "name": "Vinita Ji",
                "addresses": []
            },
            "barcodes": [
                {
                    "status": "unused",
                    "barcode": "9999989751978888894719025",
                    "created": "2023-03-04T15:06:19Z",
                    "changed": "2023-03-04T15:06:19Z",
                    "checkin_type": 0,
                    "is_printed": false
                }
            ],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Conditions for Child and Youth membership",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999991879"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Vinita",
                    "question": "Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999994149"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Child Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999998779"
                }
            ],
            "checked_in": false,
            "cancelled": false,
            "refunded": false,
            "affiliate": "oddtdteb",
            "guestlist_id": null,
            "invited_by": null,
            "status": "Attending",
            "ticket_class_name": "Weekend Membership - Tier 1",
            "delivery_method": "electronic",
            "event_id": "999998975197",
            "order_id": "8888894719",
            "ticket_class_id": "999996719"
        },
        {
            "costs": {
                "base_price": {
                    "display": "$31.92",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3192,
                    "major_value": "31.92"
                },
                "eventbrite_fee": {
                    "display": "$2.15",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 215,
                    "major_value": "2.15"
                },
                "gross": {
                    "display": "$35.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3500,
                    "major_value": "35.00"
                },
                "payment_fee": {
                    "display": "$0.93",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 93,
                    "major_value": "0.93"
                },
                "tax": {
                    "display": "$0.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 0,
                    "major_value": "0.00"
                }
            },
            "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/999998975197/attendees/0000000026/",
            "id": "0000000026",
            "changed": "2023-03-04T15:06:18Z",
            "created": "2023-03-04T15:06:16Z",
            "quantity": 1,
            "variant_id": null,
            "profile": {
                "first_name": "Allyn",
                "last_name": "Amice",
                "email": "aamice@example.com",
                "name": "Allyn Amice",
                "addresses": []
            },
            "barcodes": [
                {
                    "status": "unused",
                    "barcode": "9999989751978888894719026",
                    "created": "2023-03-04T15:06:19Z",
                    "changed": "2023-03-04T15:06:19Z",
                    "checkin_type": 0,
                    "is_printed": false
                }
            ],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Conditions for Child and Youth membership",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999991879"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Allyn",
                    "question": "Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999994149"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Child Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999998779"
                }
            ],
            "checked_in": false,
            "cancelled": false,
            "refunded": false,
            "affiliate": "oddtdteb",
            "guestlist_id": null,
            "invited_by": null,
            "status": "Attending",
            "ticket_class_name": "Weekend Membership - Tier 1",
            "delivery_method": "electronic",
            "event_id": "999998975197",
            "order_id": "8888894719",
            "ticket_class_id": "999996719"
        },
        {
            "costs": {
                "base_price": {
                    "display": "$31.92",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3192,
                    "major_value": "31.92"
                },
                "eventbrite_fee": {
                    "display": "$2.15",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 215,
                    "major_value": "2.15"
                },
                "gross": {
                    "display": "$35.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3500,
                    "major_value": "35.00"
                },
                "payment_fee": {
                    "display": "$0.93",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 93,
                    "major_value": "0.93"
                },
                "tax": {
                    "display": "$0.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 0,
                    "major_value": "0.00"
                }
            },
            "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/999998975197/attendees/0000000027/",
            "id": "0000000027",
            "changed": "2023-03-04T15:06:25Z",
            "created": "2023-03-04T15:06:22Z",
            "quantity": 1,
            "variant_id": null,
            "profile": {
                "first_name": "Danica",
                "last_name": "Ardith",
                "email": "dardith@example.com",
                "name": "Danica Ardith",
                "addresses": []
            },
            "barcodes": [
                {
                    "status": "unused",
                    "barcode": "9999989751978888804699027",
                    "created": "2023-03-04T15:06:26Z",
                    "changed": "2023-03-04T15:06:26Z",
                    "checkin_type": 0,
                    "is_printed": false
                }
            ],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Conditions for Child and Youth membership",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999991879"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Danica",
                    "question": "Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999994149"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Child Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999998779"
                }
            ],
            "checked_in": false,
            "cancelled": false,
            "refunded": false,
            "affiliate": "oddtdteb",
            "guestlist_id": null,
            "invited_by": null,
            "status": "Attending",
            "ticket_class_name": "Weekend Membership - Tier 1",
            "delivery_method": "electronic",
            "event_id": "999998975197",
            "order_id": "8888804699",
            "ticket_class_id": "999996719"
        },
        {
            "costs": {
                "base_price": {
                    "display": "$31.92",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3192,
                    "major_value": "31.92"
                },
                "eventbrite_fee": {
                    "display": "$2.15",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 215,
                    "major_value": "2.15"
                },
                "gross": {
                    "display": "$35.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3500,
                    "major_value": "35.00"
                },
                "payment_fee": {
                    "display": "$0.93",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 93,
                    "major_value": "0.93"
                },
                "tax": {
                    "display": "$0.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 0,
                    "major_value": "0.00"
                }
            },
            "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/999998975197/attendees/0000000028/",
            "id": "0000000028",
            "changed": "2023-03-04T15:06:40Z",
            "created": "2023-03-04T15:06:37Z",
            "quantity": 1,
            "variant_id": null,
            "profile": {
                "first_name": "Darci",
                "last_name": "Philana",
                "email": "dphilana@example.com",
                "name": "Darci Philana",
                "addresses": {
                    "bill": {
                        "country": "US",
                        "postal_code": "76104"
                    }
                }
            },
            "barcodes": [
                {
                    "status": "unused",
                    "barcode": "9999989751978888806979028",
                    "created": "2023-03-04T15:06:41Z",
                    "changed": "2023-03-04T15:06:41Z",
                    "checkin_type": 0,
                    "is_printed": false
                }
            ],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Conditions for Child and Youth membership",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999991879"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Darci",
                    "question": "Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999994149"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Child Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999998779"
                }
            ],
            "checked_in": false,
            "cancelled": false,
            "refunded": false,
            "affiliate": "oddtdteb",
            "guestlist_id": null,
            "invited_by": null,
            "status": "Attending",
            "ticket_class_name": "Weekend Membership - Tier 1",
            "delivery_method": "electronic",
            "event_id": "999998975197",
            "order_id": "8888806979",
            "ticket_class_id": "999996719"
        },
        {
            "costs": {
                "base_price": {
                    "display": "$31.92",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3192,
                    "major_value": "31.92"
                },
                "eventbrite_fee": {
                    "display": "$2.15",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 215,
                    "major_value": "2.15"
                },
                "gross": {
                    "display": "$35.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3500,
                    "major_value": "35.00"
                },
                "payment_fee": {
                    "display": "$0.93",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 93,
                    "major_value": "0.93"
                },
                "tax": {
                    "display": "$0.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 0,
                    "major_value": "0.00"
                }
            },
            "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/999998975197/attendees/0000000029/",
            "id": "0000000029",
            "changed": "2023-03-04T15:06:42Z",
            "created": "2023-03-04T15:06:40Z",
            "quantity": 1,
            "variant_id": null,
            "profile": {
                "first_name": "Sonnnie",
                "last_name": "Leblanc",
                "email": "sleblanc@example.com",
                "name": "Sonnnie Leblanc",
                "addresses": []
            },
            "barcodes": [
                {
                    "status": "unused",
                    "barcode": "9999989751978888807089029",
                    "created": "2023-03-04T15:06:43Z",
                    "changed": "2023-03-04T15:06:43Z",
                    "checkin_type": 0,
                    "is_printed": false
                }
            ],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Conditions for Child and Youth membership",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999991879"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Sonnnie",
                    "question": "Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999994149"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Child Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999998779"
                }
            ],
            "checked_in": false,
            "cancelled": false,
            "refunded": false,
            "affiliate": "oddtdteb",
            "guestlist_id": null,
            "invited_by": null,
            "status": "Attending",
            "ticket_class_name": "Weekend Membership - Tier 1",
            "delivery_method": "electronic",
            "event_id": "999998975197",
            "order_id": "8888807089",
            "ticket_class_id": "999996719"
        },
        {
            "costs": {
                "base_price": {
                    "display": "$31.92",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3192,
                    "major_value": "31.92"
                },
                "eventbrite_fee": {
                    "display": "$2.15",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 215,
                    "major_value": "2.15"
                },
                "gross": {
                    "display": "$35.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3500,
                    "major_value": "35.00"
                },
                "payment_fee": {
                    "display": "$0.93",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 93,
                    "major_value": "0.93"
                },
                "tax": {
                    "display": "$0.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 0,
                    "major_value": "0.00"
                }
            },
            "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/999998975197/attendees/0000000030/",
            "id": "0000000030",
            "changed": "2023-03-04T15:06:42Z",
            "created": "2023-03-04T15:06:40Z",
            "quantity": 1,
            "variant_id": null,
            "profile": {
                "first_name": "Vinnie",
                "last_name": "Adhamh",
                "email": "vadhamh@example.com",
                "name": "Vinnie Adhamh",
                "addresses": []
            },
            "barcodes": [
                {
                    "status": "unused",
                    "barcode": "9999989751978888807089030",
                    "created": "2023-03-04T15:06:43Z",
                    "changed": "2023-03-04T15:06:43Z",
                    "checkin_type": 0,
                    "is_printed": false
                }
            ],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Conditions for Child and Youth membership",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999991879"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Vinnie",
                    "question": "Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999994149"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Child Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999998779"
                }
            ],
            "checked_in": false,
            "cancelled": false,
            "refunded": false,
            "affiliate": "oddtdteb",
            "guestlist_id": null,
            "invited_by": null,
            "status": "Attending",
            "ticket_class_name": "Weekend Membership - Tier 1",
            "delivery_method": "electronic",
            "event_id": "999998975197",
            "order_id": "8888807089",
            "ticket_class_id": "999996719"
        },
        {
            "costs": {
                "base_price": {
                    "display": "$31.92",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3192,
                    "major_value": "31.92"
                },
                "eventbrite_fee": {
                    "display": "$2.15",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 215,
                    "major_value": "2.15"
                },
                "gross": {
                    "display": "$35.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3500,
                    "major_value": "35.00"
                },
                "payment_fee": {
                    "display": "$0.93",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 93,
                    "major_value": "0.93"
                },
                "tax": {
                    "display": "$0.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 0,
                    "major_value": "0.00"
                }
            },
            "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/999998975197/attendees/0000000031/",
            "id": "0000000031",
            "changed": "2023-03-04T15:07:30Z",
            "created": "2023-03-04T15:07:27Z",
            "quantity": 1,
            "variant_id": null,
            "profile": {
                "first_name": "Meggie",
                "last_name": "Figone",
                "email": "mfigone@example.com",
                "name": "Meggie Figone",
                "addresses": {
                    "bill": {
                        "country": "US",
                        "postal_code": "76003"
                    }
                }
            },
            "barcodes": [
                {
                    "status": "unused",
                    "barcode": "9999989751978888804839031",
                    "created": "2023-03-04T15:07:31Z",
                    "changed": "2023-03-04T15:07:31Z",
                    "checkin_type": 0,
                    "is_printed": false
                }
            ],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Conditions for Child and Youth membership",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999991879"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Meggie",
                    "question": "Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999994149"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Child Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999998779"
                }
            ],
            "checked_in": false,
            "cancelled": false,
            "refunded": false,
            "affiliate": "oddtdteb",
            "guestlist_id": null,
            "invited_by": null,
            "status": "Attending",
            "ticket_class_name": "Weekend Membership - Tier 1",
            "delivery_method": "electronic",
            "event_id": "999998975197",
            "order_id": "8888804839",
            "ticket_class_id": "999996719"
        },
        {
            "costs": {
                "base_price": {
                    "display": "$31.92",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3192,
                    "major_value": "31.92"
                },
                "eventbrite_fee": {
                    "display": "$2.15",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 215,
                    "major_value": "2.15"
                },
                "gross": {
                    "display": "$35.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3500,
                    "major_value": "35.00"
                },
                "payment_fee": {
                    "display": "$0.93",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 93,
                    "major_value": "0.93"
                },
                "tax": {
                    "display": "$0.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 0,
                    "major_value": "0.00"
                }
            },
            "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/999998975197/attendees/0000000032/",
            "id": "0000000032",
            "changed": "2023-03-04T15:07:34Z",
            "created": "2023-03-04T15:07:31Z",
            "quantity": 1,
            "variant_id": null,
            "profile": {
                "first_name": "Fifine",
                "last_name": "Phenice",
                "email": "fphenice@example.com",
                "name": "Fifine Phenice",
                "addresses": {
                    "bill": {
                        "country": "US",
                        "postal_code": "75038"
                    }
                }
            },
            "barcodes": [
                {
                    "status": "unused",
                    "barcode": "9999989751978888898609032",
                    "created": "2023-03-04T15:07:35Z",
                    "changed": "2023-03-04T15:07:35Z",
                    "checkin_type": 0,
                    "is_printed": false
                }
            ],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Conditions for Child and Youth membership",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999991879"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Fifine",
                    "question": "Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999994149"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Child Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999998779"
                }
            ],
            "checked_in": false,
            "cancelled": false,
            "refunded": false,
            "affiliate": "oddtdteb",
            "guestlist_id": null,
            "invited_by": null,
            "status": "Attending",
            "ticket_class_name": "Weekend Membership - Tier 1",
            "delivery_method": "electronic",
            "event_id": "999998975197",
            "order_id": "8888898609",
            "ticket_class_id": "999996719"
        },
        {
            "costs": {
                "base_price": {
                    "display": "$31.92",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3192,
                    "major_value": "31.92"
                },
                "eventbrite_fee": {
                    "display": "$2.15",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 215,
                    "major_value": "2.15"
                },
                "gross": {
                    "display": "$35.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3500,
                    "major_value": "35.00"
                },
                "payment_fee": {
                    "display": "$0.93",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 93,
                    "major_value": "0.93"
                },
                "tax": {
                    "display": "$0.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 0,
                    "major_value": "0.00"
                }
            },
            "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/999998975197/attendees/0000000033/",
            "id": "0000000033",
            "changed": "2023-03-04T15:07:34Z",
            "created": "2023-03-04T15:07:31Z",
            "quantity": 1,
            "variant_id": null,
            "profile": {
                "first_name": "Edyth",
                "last_name": "Sparks",
                "email": "esparks@example.com",
                "name": "Edyth Sparks",
                "addresses": {
                    "bill": {
                        "country": "US",
                        "postal_code": "75038"
                    }
                }
            },
            "barcodes": [
                {
                    "status": "unused",
                    "barcode": "9999989751978888898609033",
                    "created": "2023-03-04T15:07:35Z",
                    "changed": "2023-03-04T15:07:35Z",
                    "checkin_type": 0,
                    "is_printed": false
                }
            ],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Conditions for Child and Youth membership",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999991879"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Edyth",
                    "question": "Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999994149"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Child Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999998779"
                }
            ],
            "checked_in": false,
            "cancelled": false,
            "refunded": false,
            "affiliate": "oddtdteb",
            "guestlist_id": null,
            "invited_by": null,
            "status": "Attending",
            "ticket_class_name": "Weekend Membership - Tier 1",
            "delivery_method": "electronic",
            "event_id": "999998975197",
            "order_id": "8888898609",
            "ticket_class_id": "999996719"
        },
        {
            "costs": {
                "base_price": {
                    "display": "$31.92",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3192,
                    "major_value": "31.92"
                },
                "eventbrite_fee": {
                    "display": "$2.15",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 215,
                    "major_value": "2.15"
                },
                "gross": {
                    "display": "$35.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3500,
                    "major_value": "35.00"
                },
                "payment_fee": {
                    "display": "$0.93",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 93,
                    "major_value": "0.93"
                },
                "tax": {
                    "display": "$0.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 0,
                    "major_value": "0.00"
                }
            },
            "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/999998975197/attendees/0000000034/",
            "id": "0000000034",
            "changed": "2023-03-04T15:08:05Z",
            "created": "2023-03-04T15:08:02Z",
            "quantity": 1,
            "variant_id": null,
            "profile": {
                "first_name": "Keriann",
                "last_name": "Kenleigh",
                "email": "kkenleigh@example.com",
                "name": "Keriann Kenleigh",
                "addresses": {
                    "bill": {
                        "country": "US",
                        "postal_code": "76011"
                    }
                }
            },
            "barcodes": [
                {
                    "status": "unused",
                    "barcode": "9999989751978888805509034",
                    "created": "2023-03-04T15:08:06Z",
                    "changed": "2023-03-04T15:08:06Z",
                    "checkin_type": 0,
                    "is_printed": false
                }
            ],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Conditions for Child and Youth membership",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999991879"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Keriann",
                    "question": "Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999994149"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Child Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999998779"
                }
            ],
            "checked_in": false,
            "cancelled": false,
            "refunded": false,
            "affiliate": "oddtdteb",
            "guestlist_id": null,
            "invited_by": null,
            "status": "Attending",
            "ticket_class_name": "Weekend Membership - Tier 1",
            "delivery_method": "electronic",
            "event_id": "999998975197",
            "order_id": "8888805509",
            "ticket_class_id": "999996719"
        },
        {
            "costs": {
                "base_price": {
                    "display": "$31.92",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3192,
                    "major_value": "31.92"
                },
                "eventbrite_fee": {
                    "display": "$2.15",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 215,
                    "major_value": "2.15"
                },
                "gross": {
                    "display": "$35.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3500,
                    "major_value": "35.00"
                },
                "payment_fee": {
                    "display": "$0.93",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 93,
                    "major_value": "0.93"
                },
                "tax": {
                    "display": "$0.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 0,
                    "major_value": "0.00"
                }
            },
            "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/999998975197/attendees/0000000035/",
            "id": "0000000035",
            "changed": "2023-03-04T15:08:05Z",
            "created": "2023-03-04T15:08:02Z",
            "quantity": 1,
            "variant_id": null,
            "profile": {
                "first_name": "Liuka",
                "last_name": "Torhert",
                "email": "ltorhert@example.com",
                "name": "Liuka Torhert",
                "addresses": {
                    "bill": {
                        "country": "US",
                        "postal_code": "76011"
                    }
                }
            },
            "barcodes": [
                {
                    "status": "unused",
                    "barcode": "9999989751978888805509035",
                    "created": "2023-03-04T15:08:06Z",
                    "changed": "2023-03-04T15:08:06Z",
                    "checkin_type": 0,
                    "is_printed": false
                }
            ],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Conditions for Child and Youth membership",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999991879"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Liuka",
                    "question": "Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999994149"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Child Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999998779"
                }
            ],
            "checked_in": false,
            "cancelled": false,
            "refunded": false,
            "affiliate": "oddtdteb",
            "guestlist_id": null,
            "invited_by": null,
            "status": "Attending",
            "ticket_class_name": "Weekend Membership - Tier 1",
            "delivery_method": "electronic",
            "event_id": "999998975197",
            "order_id": "8888805509",
            "ticket_class_id": "999996719"
        },
        {
            "costs": {
                "base_price": {
                    "display": "$31.92",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3192,
                    "major_value": "31.92"
                },
                "eventbrite_fee": {
                    "display": "$2.15",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 215,
                    "major_value": "2.15"
                },
                "gross": {
                    "display": "$35.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3500,
                    "major_value": "35.00"
                },
                "payment_fee": {
                    "display": "$0.93",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 93,
                    "major_value": "0.93"
                },
                "tax": {
                    "display": "$0.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 0,
                    "major_value": "0.00"
                }
            },
            "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/999998975197/attendees/0000000036/",
            "id": "0000000036",
            "changed": "2023-03-04T15:08:05Z",
            "created": "2023-03-04T15:08:02Z",
            "quantity": 1,
            "variant_id": null,
            "profile": {
                "first_name": "Xylina",
                "last_name": "Soble",
                "email": "xsoble@example.com",
                "name": "Xylina Soble",
                "addresses": {
                    "bill": {
                        "country": "US",
                        "postal_code": "76011"
                    }
                }
            },
            "barcodes": [
                {
                    "status": "unused",
                    "barcode": "9999989751978888805509036",
                    "created": "2023-03-04T15:08:06Z",
                    "changed": "2023-03-04T15:08:06Z",
                    "checkin_type": 0,
                    "is_printed": false
                }
            ],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Conditions for Child and Youth membership",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999991879"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Xylina",
                    "question": "Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999994149"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Child Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999998779"
                }
            ],
            "checked_in": false,
            "cancelled": false,
            "refunded": false,
            "affiliate": "oddtdteb",
            "guestlist_id": null,
            "invited_by": null,
            "status": "Attending",
            "ticket_class_name": "Weekend Membership - Tier 1",
            "delivery_method": "electronic",
            "event_id": "999998975197",
            "order_id": "8888805509",
            "ticket_class_id": "999996719"
        },
        {
            "costs": {
                "base_price": {
                    "display": "$31.92",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3192,
                    "major_value": "31.92"
                },
                "eventbrite_fee": {
                    "display": "$2.15",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 215,
                    "major_value": "2.15"
                },
                "gross": {
                    "display": "$35.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3500,
                    "major_value": "35.00"
                },
                "payment_fee": {
                    "display": "$0.93",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 93,
                    "major_value": "0.93"
                },
                "tax": {
                    "display": "$0.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 0,
                    "major_value": "0.00"
                }
            },
            "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/999998975197/attendees/0000000037/",
            "id": "0000000037",
            "changed": "2023-03-04T15:08:05Z",
            "created": "2023-03-04T15:08:02Z",
            "quantity": 1,
            "variant_id": null,
            "profile": {
                "first_name": "Valera",
                "last_name": "Philbert",
                "email": "vphilbert@example.com",
                "name": "Valera Philbert",
                "addresses": {
                    "bill": {
                        "country": "US",
                        "postal_code": "76011"
                    }
                }
            },
            "barcodes": [
                {
                    "status": "unused",
                    "barcode": "9999989751978888805509037",
                    "created": "2023-03-04T15:08:06Z",
                    "changed": "2023-03-04T15:08:06Z",
                    "checkin_type": 0,
                    "is_printed": false
                }
            ],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Conditions for Child and Youth membership",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999991879"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Valera",
                    "question": "Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999994149"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Child Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999998779"
                }
            ],
            "checked_in": false,
            "cancelled": false,
            "refunded": false,
            "affiliate": "oddtdteb",
            "guestlist_id": null,
            "invited_by": null,
            "status": "Attending",
            "ticket_class_name": "Weekend Membership - Tier 1",
            "delivery_method": "electronic",
            "event_id": "999998975197",
            "order_id": "8888805509",
            "ticket_class_id": "999996719"
        },
        {
            "costs": {
                "base_price": {
                    "display": "$31.92",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3192,
                    "major_value": "31.92"
                },
                "eventbrite_fee": {
                    "display": "$2.15",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 215,
                    "major_value": "2.15"
                },
                "gross": {
                    "display": "$35.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3500,
                    "major_value": "35.00"
                },
                "payment_fee": {
                    "display": "$0.93",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 93,
                    "major_value": "0.93"
                },
                "tax": {
                    "display": "$0.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 0,
                    "major_value": "0.00"
                }
            },
            "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/999998975197/attendees/0000000038/",
            "id": "0000000038",
            "changed": "2023-03-04T15:08:05Z",
            "created": "2023-03-04T15:08:02Z",
            "quantity": 1,
            "variant_id": null,
            "profile": {
                "first_name": "Donelle",
                "last_name": "Booth",
                "email": "dbooth@example.com",
                "name": "Donelle Booth",
                "addresses": {
                    "bill": {
                        "country": "US",
                        "postal_code": "76011"
                    }
                }
            },
            "barcodes": [
                {
                    "status": "unused",
                    "barcode": "9999989751978888805509038",
                    "created": "2023-03-04T15:08:06Z",
                    "changed": "2023-03-04T15:08:06Z",
                    "checkin_type": 0,
                    "is_printed": false
                }
            ],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Conditions for Child and Youth membership",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999991879"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Donelle",
                    "question": "Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999994149"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Child Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999998779"
                }
            ],
            "checked_in": false,
            "cancelled": false,
            "refunded": false,
            "affiliate": "oddtdteb",
            "guestlist_id": null,
            "invited_by": null,
            "status": "Attending",
            "ticket_class_name": "Weekend Membership - Tier 1",
            "delivery_method": "electronic",
            "event_id": "999998975197",
            "order_id": "8888805509",
            "ticket_class_id": "999996719"
        },
        {
            "costs": {
                "base_price": {
                    "display": "$31.92",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3192,
                    "major_value": "31.92"
                },
                "eventbrite_fee": {
                    "display": "$2.15",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 215,
                    "major_value": "2.15"
                },
                "gross": {
                    "display": "$35.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3500,
                    "major_value": "35.00"
                },
                "payment_fee": {
                    "display": "$0.93",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 93,
                    "major_value": "0.93"
                },
                "tax": {
                    "display": "$0.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 0,
                    "major_value": "0.00"
                }
            },
            "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/999998975197/attendees/0000000039/",
            "id": "0000000039",
            "changed": "2023-03-04T15:08:12Z",
            "created": "2023-03-04T15:08:10Z",
            "quantity": 1,
            "variant_id": null,
            "profile": {
                "first_name": "Rozamond",
                "last_name": "Wendie",
                "email": "rwendie@example.com",
                "name": "Rozamond Wendie",
                "addresses": []
            },
            "barcodes": [
                {
                    "status": "unused",
                    "barcode": "9999989751978888821899039",
                    "created": "2023-03-04T15:08:13Z",
                    "changed": "2023-03-04T15:08:13Z",
                    "checkin_type": 0,
                    "is_printed": false
                }
            ],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Conditions for Child and Youth membership",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999991879"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Rozamond",
                    "question": "Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999994149"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Child Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999998779"
                }
            ],
            "checked_in": false,
            "cancelled": false,
            "refunded": false,
            "affiliate": "oddtdteb",
            "guestlist_id": null,
            "invited_by": null,
            "status": "Attending",
            "ticket_class_name": "Weekend Membership - Tier 1",
            "delivery_method": "electronic",
            "event_id": "999998975197",
            "order_id": "8888821899",
            "ticket_class_id": "999996719"
        },
        {
            "costs": {
                "base_price": {
                    "display": "$31.92",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3192,
                    "major_value": "31.92"
                },
                "eventbrite_fee": {
                    "display": "$2.15",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 215,
                    "major_value": "2.15"
                },
                "gross": {
                    "display": "$35.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3500,
                    "major_value": "35.00"
                },
                "payment_fee": {
                    "display": "$0.93",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 93,
                    "major_value": "0.93"
                },
                "tax": {
                    "display": "$0.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 0,
                    "major_value": "0.00"
                }
            },
            "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/999998975197/attendees/0000000040/",
            "id": "0000000040",
            "changed": "2023-03-04T15:08:17Z",
            "created": "2023-03-04T15:08:14Z",
            "quantity": 1,
            "variant_id": null,
            "profile": {
                "first_name": "Diane",
                "last_name": "Aronoff",
                "email": "daronoff@example.com",
                "name": "Diane Aronoff",
                "addresses": []
            },
            "barcodes": [
                {
                    "status": "unused",
                    "barcode": "9999989751978888801739040",
                    "created": "2023-03-04T15:08:17Z",
                    "changed": "2023-03-04T15:08:17Z",
                    "checkin_type": 0,
                    "is_printed": false
                }
            ],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Conditions for Child and Youth membership",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999991879"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Diane",
                    "question": "Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999994149"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Child Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999998779"
                }
            ],
            "checked_in": false,
            "cancelled": false,
            "refunded": false,
            "affiliate": "oddtdteb",
            "guestlist_id": null,
            "invited_by": null,
            "status": "Attending",
            "ticket_class_name": "Weekend Membership - Tier 1",
            "delivery_method": "electronic",
            "event_id": "999998975197",
            "order_id": "8888801739",
            "ticket_class_id": "999996719"
        },
        {
            "costs": {
                "base_price": {
                    "display": "$31.92",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3192,
                    "major_value": "31.92"
                },
                "eventbrite_fee": {
                    "display": "$2.15",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 215,
                    "major_value": "2.15"
                },
                "gross": {
                    "display": "$35.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3500,
                    "major_value": "35.00"
                },
                "payment_fee": {
                    "display": "$0.93",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 93,
                    "major_value": "0.93"
                },
                "tax": {
                    "display": "$0.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 0,
                    "major_value": "0.00"
                }
            },
            "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/999998975197/attendees/0000000041/",
            "id": "0000000041",
            "changed": "2023-03-04T15:08:43Z",
            "created": "2023-03-04T15:08:38Z",
            "quantity": 1,
            "variant_id": null,
            "profile": {
                "first_name": "Jazmin",
                "last_name": "Mayne",
                "email": "jmayne@example.com",
                "name": "Jazmin Mayne",
                "addresses": []
            },
            "barcodes": [
                {
                    "status": "unused",
                    "barcode": "9999989751978888816549041",
                    "created": "2023-03-04T15:08:43Z",
                    "changed": "2023-03-04T15:08:43Z",
                    "checkin_type": 0,
                    "is_printed": false
                }
            ],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Conditions for Child and Youth membership",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999991879"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Jazmin",
                    "question": "Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999994149"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Child Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999998779"
                }
            ],
            "checked_in": false,
            "cancelled": false,
            "refunded": false,
            "affiliate": "oddtdteb",
            "guestlist_id": null,
            "invited_by": null,
            "status": "Attending",
            "ticket_class_name": "Weekend Membership - Tier 1",
            "delivery_method": "electronic",
            "event_id": "999998975197",
            "order_id": "8888816549",
            "ticket_class_id": "999996719"
        },
        {
            "costs": {
                "base_price": {
                    "display": "$31.92",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3192,
                    "major_value": "31.92"
                },
                "eventbrite_fee": {
                    "display": "$2.15",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 215,
                    "major_value": "2.15"
                },
                "gross": {
                    "display": "$35.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3500,
                    "major_value": "35.00"
                },
                "payment_fee": {
                    "display": "$0.93",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 93,
                    "major_value": "0.93"
                },
                "tax": {
                    "display": "$0.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 0,
                    "major_value": "0.00"
                }
            },
            "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/999998975197/attendees/0000000042/",
            "id": "0000000042",
            "changed": "2023-03-04T15:09:28Z",
            "created": "2023-03-04T15:09:25Z",
            "quantity": 1,
            "variant_id": null,
            "profile": {
                "first_name": "Kassandra",
                "last_name": "Kamaria",
                "email": "kkamaria@example.com",
                "name": "Kassandra Kamaria",
                "addresses": {
                    "bill": {
                        "country": "US",
                        "postal_code": "76180"
                    }
                }
            },
            "barcodes": [
                {
                    "status": "unused",
                    "barcode": "9999989751978888890119042",
                    "created": "2023-03-04T15:09:28Z",
                    "changed": "2023-03-04T15:09:28Z",
                    "checkin_type": 0,
                    "is_printed": false
                }
            ],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Conditions for Child and Youth membership",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999991879"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Kassandra",
                    "question": "Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999994149"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Child Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999998779"
                }
            ],
            "checked_in": false,
            "cancelled": false,
            "refunded": false,
            "affiliate": "oddtdteb",
            "guestlist_id": null,
            "invited_by": null,
            "status": "Attending",
            "ticket_class_name": "Weekend Membership - Tier 1",
            "delivery_method": "electronic",
            "event_id": "999998975197",
            "order_id": "8888890119",
            "ticket_class_id": "999996719"
        },
        {
            "costs": {
                "base_price": {
                    "display": "$31.92",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3192,
                    "major_value": "31.92"
                },
                "eventbrite_fee": {
                    "display": "$2.15",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 215,
                    "major_value": "2.15"
                },
                "gross": {
                    "display": "$35.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3500,
                    "major_value": "35.00"
                },
                "payment_fee": {
                    "display": "$0.93",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 93,
                    "major_value": "0.93"
                },
                "tax": {
                    "display": "$0.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 0,
                    "major_value": "0.00"
                }
            },
            "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/999998975197/attendees/0000000043/",
            "id": "0000000043",
            "changed": "2023-03-04T15:09:28Z",
            "created": "2023-03-04T15:09:25Z",
            "quantity": 1,
            "variant_id": null,
            "profile": {
                "first_name": "Ana",
                "last_name": "Genesia",
                "email": "agenesia@example.com",
                "name": "Ana Genesia",
                "addresses": {
                    "bill": {
                        "country": "US",
                        "postal_code": "76180"
                    }
                }
            },
            "barcodes": [
                {
                    "status": "unused",
                    "barcode": "9999989751978888890119043",
                    "created": "2023-03-04T15:09:28Z",
                    "changed": "2023-03-04T15:09:28Z",
                    "checkin_type": 0,
                    "is_printed": false
                }
            ],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Conditions for Child and Youth membership",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999991879"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Ana",
                    "question": "Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999994149"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Child Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999998779"
                }
            ],
            "checked_in": false,
            "cancelled": false,
            "refunded": false,
            "affiliate": "oddtdteb",
            "guestlist_id": null,
            "invited_by": null,
            "status": "Attending",
            "ticket_class_name": "Weekend Membership - Tier 1",
            "delivery_method": "electronic",
            "event_id": "999998975197",
            "order_id": "8888890119",
            "ticket_class_id": "999996719"
        },
        {
            "costs": {
                "base_price": {
                    "display": "$31.92",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3192,
                    "major_value": "31.92"
                },
                "eventbrite_fee": {
                    "display": "$2.15",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 215,
                    "major_value": "2.15"
                },
                "gross": {
                    "display": "$35.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3500,
                    "major_value": "35.00"
                },
                "payment_fee": {
                    "display": "$0.93",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 93,
                    "major_value": "0.93"
                },
                "tax": {
                    "display": "$0.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 0,
                    "major_value": "0.00"
                }
            },
            "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/999998975197/attendees/0000000044/",
            "id": "0000000044",
            "changed": "2023-03-04T15:09:44Z",
            "created": "2023-03-04T15:09:40Z",
            "quantity": 1,
            "variant_id": null,
            "profile": {
                "first_name": "Dasi",
                "last_name": "Danna",
                "email": "ddanna@example.com",
                "name": "Dasi Danna",
                "addresses": []
            },
            "barcodes": [
                {
                    "status": "unused",
                    "barcode": "9999989751978888828009044",
                    "created": "2023-03-04T15:09:45Z",
                    "changed": "2023-03-04T15:09:45Z",
                    "checkin_type": 0,
                    "is_printed": false
                }
            ],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Conditions for Child and Youth membership",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999991879"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Dasi",
                    "question": "Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999994149"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Child Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999998779"
                }
            ],
            "checked_in": false,
            "cancelled": false,
            "refunded": false,
            "affiliate": "oddtdteb",
            "guestlist_id": null,
            "invited_by": null,
            "status": "Attending",
            "ticket_class_name": "Weekend Membership - Tier 1",
            "delivery_method": "electronic",
            "event_id": "999998975197",
            "order_id": "8888828009",
            "ticket_class_id": "999996719"
        },
        {
            "costs": {
                "base_price": {
                    "display": "$31.92",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3192,
                    "major_value": "31.92"
                },
                "eventbrite_fee": {
                    "display": "$2.15",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 215,
                    "major_value": "2.15"
                },
                "gross": {
                    "display": "$35.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3500,
                    "major_value": "35.00"
                },
                "payment_fee": {
                    "display": "$0.93",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 93,
                    "major_value": "0.93"
                },
                "tax": {
                    "display": "$0.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 0,
                    "major_value": "0.00"
                }
            },
            "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/999998975197/attendees/0000000045/",
            "id": "0000000045",
            "changed": "2023-03-04T15:10:36Z",
            "created": "2023-03-04T15:10:31Z",
            "quantity": 1,
            "variant_id": null,
            "profile": {
                "first_name": "Gnni",
                "last_name": "Eatton",
                "email": "geatton@example.com",
                "name": "Gnni Eatton",
                "addresses": []
            },
            "barcodes": [
                {
                    "status": "unused",
                    "barcode": "9999989751978888835909045",
                    "created": "2023-03-04T15:10:37Z",
                    "changed": "2023-03-04T15:10:37Z",
                    "checkin_type": 0,
                    "is_printed": false
                }
            ],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Conditions for Child and Youth membership",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999991879"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Gnni",
                    "question": "Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999994149"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Child Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999998779"
                }
            ],
            "checked_in": false,
            "cancelled": false,
            "refunded": false,
            "affiliate": "oddtdteb",
            "guestlist_id": null,
            "invited_by": null,
            "status": "Attending",
            "ticket_class_name": "Weekend Membership - Tier 1",
            "delivery_method": "electronic",
            "event_id": "999998975197",
            "order_id": "8888835909",
            "ticket_class_id": "999996719"
        },
        {
            "costs": {
                "base_price": {
                    "display": "$31.92",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3192,
                    "major_value": "31.92"
                },
                "eventbrite_fee": {
                    "display": "$2.15",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 215,
                    "major_value": "2.15"
                },
                "gross": {
                    "display": "$35.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3500,
                    "major_value": "35.00"
                },
                "payment_fee": {
                    "display": "$0.93",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 93,
                    "major_value": "0.93"
                },
                "tax": {
                    "display": "$0.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 0,
                    "major_value": "0.00"
                }
            },
            "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/999998975197/attendees/0000000046/",
            "id": "0000000046",
            "changed": "2023-03-04T15:12:33Z",
            "created": "2023-03-04T15:12:29Z",
            "quantity": 1,
            "variant_id": null,
            "profile": {
                "first_name": "Queenie",
                "last_name": "Northway",
                "email": "qnorthway@example.com",
                "name": "Queenie Northway",
                "addresses": {
                    "bill": {
                        "country": "US",
                        "postal_code": "75428"
                    }
                }
            },
            "barcodes": [
                {
                    "status": "unused",
                    "barcode": "9999989751978888802039046",
                    "created": "2023-03-04T15:12:33Z",
                    "changed": "2023-03-04T15:12:33Z",
                    "checkin_type": 0,
                    "is_printed": false
                }
            ],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Conditions for Child and Youth membership",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999991879"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Queenie",
                    "question": "Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999994149"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Child Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999998779"
                }
            ],
            "checked_in": false,
            "cancelled": false,
            "refunded": false,
            "affiliate": "oddtdteb",
            "guestlist_id": null,
            "invited_by": null,
            "status": "Attending",
            "ticket_class_name": "Weekend Membership - Tier 1",
            "delivery_method": "electronic",
            "event_id": "999998975197",
            "order_id": "8888802039",
            "ticket_class_id": "999996719"
        },
        {
            "costs": {
                "base_price": {
                    "display": "$31.92",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3192,
                    "major_value": "31.92"
                },
                "eventbrite_fee": {
                    "display": "$2.15",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 215,
                    "major_value": "2.15"
                },
                "gross": {
                    "display": "$35.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3500,
                    "major_value": "35.00"
                },
                "payment_fee": {
                    "display": "$0.93",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 93,
                    "major_value": "0.93"
                },
                "tax": {
                    "display": "$0.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 0,
                    "major_value": "0.00"
                }
            },
            "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/999998975197/attendees/0000000047/",
            "id": "0000000047",
            "changed": "2023-03-04T15:12:33Z",
            "created": "2023-03-04T15:12:29Z",
            "quantity": 1,
            "variant_id": null,
            "profile": {
                "first_name": "Gilligan",
                "last_name": "Glantz",
                "email": "gglantz@example.com",
                "name": "Gilligan Glantz",
                "addresses": {
                    "bill": {
                        "country": "US",
                        "postal_code": "75428"
                    }
                }
            },
            "barcodes": [
                {
                    "status": "unused",
                    "barcode": "9999989751978888802039047",
                    "created": "2023-03-04T15:12:33Z",
                    "changed": "2023-03-04T15:12:33Z",
                    "checkin_type": 0,
                    "is_printed": false
                }
            ],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Conditions for Child and Youth membership",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999991879"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Gilligan",
                    "question": "Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999994149"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Child Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999998779"
                }
            ],
            "checked_in": false,
            "cancelled": false,
            "refunded": false,
            "affiliate": "oddtdteb",
            "guestlist_id": null,
            "invited_by": null,
            "status": "Attending",
            "ticket_class_name": "Weekend Membership - Tier 1",
            "delivery_method": "electronic",
            "event_id": "999998975197",
            "order_id": "8888802039",
            "ticket_class_id": "999996719"
        },
        {
            "costs": {
                "base_price": {
                    "display": "$31.92",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3192,
                    "major_value": "31.92"
                },
                "eventbrite_fee": {
                    "display": "$2.15",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 215,
                    "major_value": "2.15"
                },
                "gross": {
                    "display": "$35.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3500,
                    "major_value": "35.00"
                },
                "payment_fee": {
                    "display": "$0.93",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 93,
                    "major_value": "0.93"
                },
                "tax": {
                    "display": "$0.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 0,
                    "major_value": "0.00"
                }
            },
            "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/999998975197/attendees/0000000048/",
            "id": "0000000048",
            "changed": "2023-03-04T15:12:33Z",
            "created": "2023-03-04T15:12:29Z",
            "quantity": 1,
            "variant_id": null,
            "profile": {
                "first_name": "Aili",
                "last_name": "Yunick",
                "email": "ayunick@example.com",
                "name": "Aili Yunick",
                "addresses": {
                    "bill": {
                        "country": "US",
                        "postal_code": "75428"
                    }
                }
            },
            "barcodes": [
                {
                    "status": "unused",
                    "barcode": "9999989751978888802039048",
                    "created": "2023-03-04T15:12:33Z",
                    "changed": "2023-03-04T15:12:33Z",
                    "checkin_type": 0,
                    "is_printed": false
                }
            ],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Conditions for Child and Youth membership",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999991879"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Aili",
                    "question": "Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999994149"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Child Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999998779"
                }
            ],
            "checked_in": false,
            "cancelled": false,
            "refunded": false,
            "affiliate": "oddtdteb",
            "guestlist_id": null,
            "invited_by": null,
            "status": "Attending",
            "ticket_class_name": "Weekend Membership - Tier 1",
            "delivery_method": "electronic",
            "event_id": "999998975197",
            "order_id": "8888802039",
            "ticket_class_id": "999996719"
        },
        {
            "costs": {
                "base_price": {
                    "display": "$31.92",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3192,
                    "major_value": "31.92"
                },
                "eventbrite_fee": {
                    "display": "$2.15",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 215,
                    "major_value": "2.15"
                },
                "gross": {
                    "display": "$35.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3500,
                    "major_value": "35.00"
                },
                "payment_fee": {
                    "display": "$0.93",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 93,
                    "major_value": "0.93"
                },
                "tax": {
                    "display": "$0.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 0,
                    "major_value": "0.00"
                }
            },
            "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/999998975197/attendees/0000000049/",
            "id": "0000000049",
            "changed": "2023-03-04T15:12:33Z",
            "created": "2023-03-04T15:12:29Z",
            "quantity": 1,
            "variant_id": null,
            "profile": {
                "first_name": "Becca",
                "last_name": "Simsar",
                "email": "bsimsar@example.com",
                "name": "Becca Simsar",
                "addresses": {
                    "bill": {
                        "country": "US",
                        "postal_code": "75428"
                    }
                }
            },
            "barcodes": [
                {
                    "status": "unused",
                    "barcode": "9999989751978888802039049",
                    "created": "2023-03-04T15:12:33Z",
                    "changed": "2023-03-04T15:12:33Z",
                    "checkin_type": 0,
                    "is_printed": false
                }
            ],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Conditions for Child and Youth membership",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999991879"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Becca",
                    "question": "Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999994149"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Child Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999998779"
                }
            ],
            "checked_in": false,
            "cancelled": false,
            "refunded": false,
            "affiliate": "oddtdteb",
            "guestlist_id": null,
            "invited_by": null,
            "status": "Attending",
            "ticket_class_name": "Weekend Membership - Tier 1",
            "delivery_method": "electronic",
            "event_id": "999998975197",
            "order_id": "8888802039",
            "ticket_class_id": "999996719"
        },
        {
            "costs": {
                "base_price": {
                    "display": "$31.92",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3192,
                    "major_value": "31.92"
                },
                "eventbrite_fee": {
                    "display": "$2.15",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 215,
                    "major_value": "2.15"
                },
                "gross": {
                    "display": "$35.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 3500,
                    "major_value": "35.00"
                },
                "payment_fee": {
                    "display": "$0.93",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 93,
                    "major_value": "0.93"
                },
                "tax": {
                    "display": "$0.00",
                    "currency": "USD",
                    "value": 0,
                    "major_value": "0.00"
                }
            },
            "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/999998975197/attendees/0000000050/",
            "id": "0000000050",
            "changed": "2023-03-04T15:12:33Z",
            "created": "2023-03-04T15:12:29Z",
            "quantity": 1,
            "variant_id": null,
            "profile": {
                "first_name": "Glenda",
                "last_name": "Rolo",
                "email": "grolo@example.com",
                "name": "Glenda Rolo",
                "addresses": {
                    "bill": {
                        "country": "US",
                        "postal_code": "75428"
                    }
                }
            },
            "barcodes": [
                {
                    "status": "unused",
                    "barcode": "9999989751978888802039050",
                    "created": "2023-03-04T15:12:33Z",
                    "changed": "2023-03-04T15:12:33Z",
                    "checkin_type": 0,
                    "is_printed": false
                }
            ],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Conditions for Child and Youth membership",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999991879"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Glenda",
                    "question": "Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999994149"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Child Badge Name",
                    "type": "text",
                    "question_id": "999998779"
                }
            ],
            "checked_in": false,
            "cancelled": false,
            "refunded": false,
            "affiliate": "oddtdteb",
            "guestlist_id": null,
            "invited_by": null,
            "status": "Attending",
            "ticket_class_name": "Weekend Membership - Tier 1",
            "delivery_method": "electronic",
            "event_id": "999998975197",
            "order_id": "8888802039",
            "ticket_class_id": "999996719"
        }
    ]
}